<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anthony Lynch</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anthony Lynch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Copy Weight To Verts Tool</title>
      <link>/copy-vert-weight-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/copy-vert-weight-script/</guid>
      <description>Copy Vert Weights tool was created in a day to help with those pesky moments when you want to copy weights to certain verts. This tool help you manage the selections and copy weights quickly.&#xA;Download Link: GitHub/Rig-No-Jutsu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Changer Script</title>
      <link>/color-changer-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/color-changer-script/</guid>
      <description>Color Changer is an updated python version of a mel script(edmxColorChanger.mel) I&amp;rsquo;ve been using in my workflow. I also took this as a challenge to build a gui using cmds. I also added the ability to easily change the color on the shape of the control.&#xA;Download Link: GitHub/Rig-No-Jutsu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my website. This is my first attempt at building a Hugo site. The experience has been quite empowering and I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot of tools along the way. Its great how far web building tools have come along, I&amp;rsquo;d encourge any tech artist to give it a try.&#xA;Now that the setup is done, let the content flow! Sit tight, relax and look around. Hopefully you can find something of value here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been an Animation Industry Professional for over 10 years, and spent a majority of that time as a Rigging Artist working on projects from Animation to VFX. I specialize in creating rigging systems using python and various DCC software. I pride myself in providing animators with flexible and responsive rigs. And I really enjoy the gratifcaiton I get from solving technical problems.&#xA;Tools I&amp;rsquo;m Using Maya, UE5, Blender PyCharm/VSCode Vim Git Rocky Linux Contact Me Email: rigger@anthonylynch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reel</title>
      <link>/reel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/reel/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rig-No-Jutsu</title>
      <link>/rig-no-jutsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/rig-no-jutsu/</guid>
      <description>Here is a collection of Maya tools I created during daily work. Its only a few for now, but I have a few in the works that will be release soon.&#xA;GitHub Repo:&#xA;Download Name Description Github Color Changer For changing the color on controls and shapes. More Info Github Copy Vert Weight Tool for selecting and copying weight to verts. More Info </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/tools/</guid>
      <description>Here is a collection of Maya tools I created during daily work. Its only a few for now, but I have a few in the works that will be release soon.&#xA;GitHub Repo:&#xA;Download Name Description Github Color Changer For changing the color on controls and shapes. More Info Github Copy Vert Weight Tool for selecting and copying weight to verts. More Info </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
